cashbackholic.com 2018-05-14

# Privacy Policy - CashbackHolic.com

Protecting your privacy is important to us. We hope the following statement will help you understand how CashbackHolic.com collects, uses and safeguards the personal information you may provide to us on our site.

**What data we collect and why**  
CashbackHolic.com is created to maximize the purchasing power of your pocket dollars by collecting cash back rate information from web sites (Providers) that provide cash back rebate when you shop online through their affiliated stores. Currently, we only collect personal email address provided by a visitor who made review comments. CashbackHolic.com may collect the data of the internet browsers that access or attempt to access our websites. The data we collected will be solely used for browser compatibility improvement purpose and will not be shared with any third party.

**How we keep your information secure**  
The security of your personal information is important to CashbackHolic.com. If personal information is collected in the future, CashbackHolic.com will use a secure, encrypted connection (called an SSL connection) on all pages where you access or transmit personal information.

**Your privacy with CashbackHolic.com**  
CashbackHolic.com will never ask for your name, age, sex, physical address or any other personal information in an unsolicited phone call, email or letter. Further, any contact with CashbackHolic.com support in which personal information may be exchanged with a customer service representative will be used only for the purpose of satisfying your request. Any personal information you provide will not be recorded or used for any reason beyond that of the stated request.

If we change our privacy policy, we will post a change notice to this privacy statement and other appropriate places. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it regularly. If we make changes to this policy, we may notify you, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**Your privacy with our partners and advertisers**  
CashbackHolic.com does not record personal information passed from our visitors to affiliated stores. Order information, including order numbers and amounts, may be available to CashbackHolic.com, the Providers, the store, or third party affiliate program management companies for accurate tracking purposes, but this information will not be released by CashbackHolic.com to other parties.

CashbackHolic.com contains links to various sites. Each of these sites has a privacy policy that may differ from that of CashbackHolic.com. Please refer to the relevant store's privacy and opt-out policy.

**Our policies on email**  
CashbackHolic.com may send emails to our visitors only when a visitor contacts us to report issues, request for information, or provide suggestions.

**Cookies and how are they used**  
Cookies are small text files that a web site can write to your computer. We may use cookies to help your search experience. Cookies are also used by many of our partners, Providers, and advertisers to identify you.

**Your choices and responsibilities**  
We will post all changes to this Privacy Agreement here on our site. You are responsible for checking periodically on policy updates.

For any questions, please contact us at [support@cashbackholic.com](mailto:support@cashbackholic.com?subject=Re%3A%20Privacy%20Policy).

CashbackHolic.com  
October 12, 2014
